Weini(Frankie) Zhong



Summary

With over 5 years of graphic design experience with web design and coding skills, I have developed proficiency in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, and After Effects. I am actively seeking a Graphic Design opportunity where I can apply my extensive skills to create impactful visual content.

zhongweini0703@gmail.com (437) 974-0230 Toronto, ON M2R 2C5 LinkedIn Portfolio GitHub

Education

Seneca College

Interactive Media Design
Toronto, Canada
Sept. 2022 - May. 2024
Tech-savvy Assistant at Seneca Sandbox
Teaching Assistant(Web Development)

Luxun Academy of Fine Arts

Bachelor of Arts (Dyeing and Weaving Art Design) Shenyang, China Sept. 2011 - July. 2015

Skills

Design Tool & Platforms:

Over 5 years of expertise in graphic design with proficiency in Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator. Competent in using Figma, Premiere pro, Adobe Effect, Adobe Lightroom, GitHub, Netlify, Wordpress.

Programming skills:

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Sass, API integration, jQuery and React.

Soft Skills:

Teamwork, Problem Solving, Active learning, Communication, Dependability

Language

English, Chinese, Cantonese

Interests

Photography, video games, hiking, rock climbing, scuba diving

Experience

Graphic Designer

SOUNDASIA Technology Co., Ltd.

Shenzhen, China

Sept. 2020 - Aug. 2022

- Specialized in graphic design for a diverse range of products, including but not limited to wall art, cards, greeting cards, bookmarks, and holiday decorations (Christmas, Thanksgiving, Valentine's Day, New Year, St. Patrick's Day).
- Utilized Photoshop and Illustrator for designing and refining graphics.
- Translated product development's requirements into visually appealing and compliant designs, ensuring they were seamlessly applied to the final products.
- Assisted in the confirmation of product samples, communicating with manufacturers about craftsmanship details, and making design adjustments in terms of size and color. Organized product design drafts and files for easy access.

Led graphic design for diverse products, achieving 50% of them surpassing 1,000 monthly sales, and 30% over 2,000, through excellent communication, adaptability, and problem-solving skills.

Fashion Graphic Designer

DEARKIDS FASHION Co., Ltd. ANNIL Co., Ltd.

Shenzhen, China May. 2019 - Sept. 2020 Jul. 2018 - Jun. 2019

- Create various clothing patterns, including but not limited to textures, prints, and graphic elements.
- Utilized Adobe Creative software (Photoshop and Illustrator) to craft original illustrations and graphics.
- Collaborated closely with fashion designers and product development teams, etc., to ensure patterns coordinate with clothing designs.
- Produced detailed product craft files, including specifications for size, color, materials, and processes.
- Collaborated with the procurement team and factories to ensure the feasibility and cost-effectiveness.
- Maintained and organized design and printing documents for easy access and reference.

Additional

- In 2018, participated in PADI AWARE Foundation's underwater cleaning in the Philippines, collecting survey data on underwater garbage.
- Volunteered at Pride Toronto Street Fair, ensuring booth cleanliness, providing event information, and promoting diversity in June 2023.